musicthinktank.com 2004-02-14

# 

**SearchPort Privacy Statement**

_**POLICY OVERVIEW**_

Welcome to SearchPort’s privacy policy. We at NetVisibilty view the protection of individual privacy as critically important, and we are committed to maintaining the highest standards in the industry. It is our fundamental goal at NetVisibilty to remain a leader in internet-enabled marketing and advertising, while maintaining our commitment to these standards.

The following is SearchPort’s overall company policy related to privacy, as well as a summary of your choice to Opt-Out of our information collection practices. This policy is open to comment and is meant to provide an evolving framework from which we at NetVisibilty can address any concerns of the Internet community.

For more information, or if you have questions or concerns regarding SearchPort’s Privacy Statement, please send us an e-mail at info@netvisibility.com or you can send correspondence to the following address:

Privacy  
SearchPort.  
7700 Irvine Center Drive  
Suite 800  
Irvine CA 92618

_**COMPANY PRACTICES**_

The following statement describes the overall company practices of Searchport.com, including advertising on our network of websites, as well as across other internal sites, and products and services that are offered by Searchport.com.

**INFORMATION COLLECTED BY SEARCHPORT**

**_Non-Personally Identifiable Consumer Data_**

At SearchPort we collect what is known as "Click Stream Data." Click Stream Data is anonymous, and includes information such as a web surfer's IP address, web pages which have been viewed by a web surfer, date and time, domain type, and responses by a web surfer to an advertisement delivered by us.

As a part of the registration process, we may request and collect additional non-personally identifiable information about the visitor. Examples of the non-personally identifiable data that may be requested include age, gender, and interests. None of the foregoing information (collectively referred to as "non-personally identifiable data"), by itself, or together, can by its nature be tracked to a specific individual. Web surfers may elect not to provide Click Stream Data by following the Cookie Opt-Out procedures set forth below. In addition, web surfers who have provided registration data may elect to have their data deleted from our files, or kept from being used for purposes other than for the service requested.

**_Personally-Identifiable Consumer Data_**

SearchPort will on occasion ask people to register to receive additional information or so that we may contact the individual for follow up. This information is never sold to any other agency or individual for any other use. Examples of personally-identifiable data that may be requested include name, address, and e-mail address.

**HOW COLLECTED INFORMATION IS USED**

The non-personally identifiable data that SearchPort collects is used for marketing and sales efforts to better target advertisements and other content to individuals in an effort to create a personally relevant experience for each person. The data is also used to predict responses to advertisements, and to help determine which ads perform best and which content is most appropriate for different individuals.

If a consumer elects to provide SearchPort with personally-identifiable data, we may utilize such data for marketing purposes. In addition, that data may be combined with information collected from other sources to assist with targeting ads to that consumer's preferences and behaviors.

**SHARING WITH THIRD-PARTIES**

All personally-identifiable data provided by individuals is maintained in strict confidence by SearchPort and will be treated with the same level of respect and care that SearchPort treats its other proprietary information and trade secrets.

In the event that NetVisibilty or part(s) of the company, may one day be purchased by, or merged with, another company. If that's the case, the acquiring (or merging) company will have access to your information.

Finally, SearchPort may share information on individuals as it deems necessary to comply and cooperate with government and law enforcement officials.

**CONSUMER CHOICE**

**_Changes To Our Privacy Policy_**

The issue of privacy is an evolving one. NetVisibilty is committed to the constant monitoring and examination of its privacy practices, and may, from time to time, institute changes to its privacy policy. In the event that any material changes are made to the company's privacy practices, we will promptly make changes to this privacy policy that discloses the changes.

**_Contacting Us_**

For more information, or if you have questions or concerns regarding SearchPort’s privacy practices, please send us an e-mail at [info@netvisibilty.com](mailto:info@netvisibilty.com), or you can send correspondence to the following address:

Privacy  
SearchPort.  
7700 Irvine Center Drive  
Suite 800  
Irvine CA 92618
